

ICOR MIROWSKI

My passion for technology and programming has stemmed from my previous role in the finance industry, where I had an opportunity to see the application of data and how it can be used in the world of technology.

This sparked me into teaching myself the basics and building foundation from online resources like Codecademy and W3Schools. During my spare time, I love to keep myself fit by going to the gym and running. I love to travel and experience new places. I am open and excited for new things that may come into my life and career.

SUMMARY

I am a graduate from Queen Mary University with 2 years' experience in Business and Management. I am currently training as a tech trainee with future proof towards my career change into tech industry.

Looking for an opportunities where I could build strong foundation of programming knowledge with the support of professionals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

futureproof | Tech Trainee | April 2022 - July 2022

- 13-week bootcamp covering the main areas of web development, including JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Databases, and Python.
- Currently working on group projects, portfolio and my own website. The outcome will be available in a few weeks.

Nordea Bank Abp | Assistant Service Operations Officer | April 2021 - April 2022

- Worked within the Global Danish settlement team, involving daily settlement of various global securities. Working within a Scandinavian environment.
- Improved problem-solving and analytical skills by maintaining relevant liquidity on internal bank's accounts. Strengthen my attention to detail and clear concise communication via support internal stakeholders regarding securities settlement.

Virgin Active | Service Manager | January 2019 - August 2019

- Management and development of department's budget, ensuring all financial targets are achieved.
- Management of two small diverse teams: including recruitment, training, development & performance management, as well as rota's, payroll and day to day management.

EDUCATION

Queen Mary University of London | Sep 2017 - Dec 2018 |

MSc Business Management

DeMontfort University, Leicester | Sep 2015 - Jan 2016 |

BSc Business Studies - Exchange student

University of Lodz | Sep 2013 - Jul 2016 |

BSc International Relations spec. International Marketing

FIND OUT MORE



GitHub



Igor Mirowsk

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Command Line Interface

Git/GitHub

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Python

Bootstrap

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Leadership & team development

Problem solving

Time management

Communication

Project management

Attention to detail